很少有人调到这儿来  你是哪人
You don't get too many transfer at this place. Where you from?
奥尔巴尼  能来大城市我真激动
Albany. I'm just so excited to be in the big city.
别太开心了
Yeah, well, don't get too excited.
跟在奥尔巴尼打扫房间不会有什么两样
Same rooms as the ones you cleaned in Albany.
床一样  地毯一样  每天早上都乱得要死
Same beds, same carpets, same mess every morning.
老天啊
Oh, my god.
那是咖啡味儿吗
Do I smell coffee?
如果有  一定是家养小精灵煮的
If you do, it was made by elves.
天呐
Geez!
你吓着我了
You scared me.
是啊  这一大早上够刺激的
Yeah, I think we all just kick-started our day.
你怎么在这儿
What are you doing here?
我昨晚做家教做到很晚
Oh, my tutoring job went late,
又没有城铁回我那儿
and the train wasn't running back to my place,
就在这儿过夜了  希望你不介意
so I crashed here. Hope you don't mind.
当然不介意了  话说
No! No, of course not. Matter of fact,
既然你跟男朋友分手了
um, now that you've broken up with your boyfriend,
其实你完全可以搬回来啊
there's really no reason you can't move back in here.
其实我真的不可以
Actually, there are many reasons,
首先  我有份租约
starting with "I have a lease."
我说过这我能想办法
Ah. I told you I would help you with that.
而且你知道我不希望你一个人住那儿
And you know I-I don't like you living in that place alone.
老爸  没事的  我应付得来
Dad, it's fine. I can handle it.
我得走了  早上还有课
I got to go. I have an early class.
早上就有案子
And we have an early murder.
她跟派一起住的时候是一码事
Well, it was one thing when she was living there with Pi,
但现在她一个人了
But now that she's alone,
为什么不离开那鬼地方  回家住呢
why not dump the dump and come home?
或许她在享受独立的感觉啊
Well, maybe she's enjoying her independence.
她没时间独立
She doesn't have time for independence.
她得去做家教  上课  实践工作
She's got her tutoring gigs, her classes, her work-study job.
她都累坏了
She's exhausted.
卡塞尔  她这人挺固执的
Well, Castle, I mean, she's strong-willed.
或许是放不下面子
Maybe it's pride.
如果真是那个原因  应该会更自豪一些
If it were pride, she'd be more... well, proud.
有别的原因
No, there's something else...
她有其他不肯回家的理由
Another reason why she's not coming home.
-西托  -诶
- Sito! - Yeah.
有人没能退房吗
Someone miss a check-out?
他倒是死翘翘了
No, he checked out, all right.
客房服务员发现贾斯汀·马奎特
Housekeeping found this guy, Justin Marquette,
死在147房间里
dead in room 147.
驾照上写着他就住在附近
His driver's license says he lives nearby.
胸口中一枪吗
Single gunshot to the chest?
一枪致命
One is all it took.
从入口伤来看  应该是小口径手枪
Based on the entry wound, I'd say a small-caliber handgun.
尸僵和肝温度
Lividity and liver temp
表明死亡时间是昨晚10点到午夜
put the time of death between 10:00 p.m. and midnight.
直到早上才被人发现吗
And he wasn't found until morning?
那怎么没人听到枪声呢
So how come no one heard the shot?
周围的房间都是空的
All the neighboring rooms are empty.
经理说只有40%的客房有住客
The manager says that the place is only about 40% occupied.
经理说他入住的时候有人跟他一起吗
Did the manager mention him checking in with anyone?
房间登记在他一人名下
The room was in his name alone.
莱恩在找昨晚的前台接待
Ryan's trying to track down the desk clerk from last night
看能不能得到更详细的信息
to see if he can get some more details.
不过没有强行闯入的迹象
There's no sign of forced entry, though.
那么凶手不是跟他一起来的
So either the killer was with him,
-就是被死者放进来的  -对
- or the victim let him in. - Yeah.
看来他从小冰箱拿了一瓶水
It looks like he took a bottle of water from this mini-fridge,
转过身来就被枪击
turned back around, got shot,
然后把椅子也拽倒了
and then he took the chair down with him.
没有行李
There's no luggage.
你说他就住在附近  那他来这儿干什么
You said he lives nearby. What was he doing here?
不知道  我看了他的手机
I don't know. I checked his phone.
没有迹象表明他要跟谁碰面
There was no indication of a meeting.
在他死前几小时
There was no appointments, calls, or texts
没有约会  电话  或短信
in the hours leading up to his death.
我找到了给贾斯汀·马奎特登记入住的前台
Hey. Found the desk clerk who checked in Justin Marquette.
这家伙有问题
Something's up with this guy.
马奎特先生大概八点来的
Uh, Mr. Marquette came at about 8:00.
没有预定  这不算不寻常
No reservation, which is not unusual.
简  跟他们说说房间的事
Jane, tell them about the room.
这的确不寻常
Well, that was unusual.
他要求住在147号房间
He asked to stay in room 147.
而且还坚持要住那儿
In fact, he insisted on it.
147号房间有什么特别的吗
Is there anything special about 147?
没有  所有房间都是一样的
No, all our rooms are identical.
所以我才觉得奇怪
That's why it was so strange.
他以前来过吗
Had he been here before?
系统里查不到他
Well, he's not in the system,
所以他从没在任何一家最佳旅伴酒店入住过
which means he's never been a guest at any Best Traveler Hotel.
他提到他为什么要入住了吗
Did he mention why he was staying?
他不用说啊
He didn't have to.
长得挺帅  不带行李  只住一晚
Good-looking guy, no bags, checking in for one night?
依我的经验  他一定是来约炮的
In my experience, that means he was here to hook up.
他跟谁一起来的吗
Did he come here with anyone?
没有  但他在跟谁发短信
No, but he was texting with someone.
我猜那一定是他约好的人
I figured that's who he was meeting.
他发了短信  你确定
He texted? Are you sure?
我们在他手机上没发现短信
We didn't find any texts on his phone.
我确定
I'm positive.
看
There.
看到没  他在发短信
See? He's texting.
而且是用翻盖手机
On a flip phone.
那不是我们找到的手机
That's not the phone we found.
就我能查到的看
As far as I can tell,
这是贾斯汀·马奎特名下唯一的手机
that's the only cellphone registered to Justin Marquette.
那么我们在监控里看到的一定是另一部秘密手机
So the one we saw in the video must be a second, secret one.
而凶手为了掩藏身份给拿走了
Which the killer took to hide their identity.
那么这人是谁
So who is this guy,
为什么要用第二部手机  为什么非待在那间房
why a second phone, and why room 147?
酒店监控没有多少信息
I didn't get much from hotel security video.
覆盖面不全  而且贾斯汀房间外面的
Coverage is sketchy, and there are no cameras
走廊上没有摄像头
in the hallway outside Justin's room.
跟他的亲属联系上了吗
Did you get ahold of next of kin?
还没  但我在他的个人网站上
Not yet, but I did find out about our victim
查到了一些东西
through his personal website.
他还有个人网站
He's got his own website?
对  他是一名演员
Yeah, he was an actor --
从信用等级来看  混得不怎么样
a struggling one, judging by his credits.
贾斯汀·马奎特
"Justin Marquette
是鲁斯特戏剧公司的成员
is a member of the Rooster Theater Company
目前正在出演
and is currently appearing
该公司的外外外百老汇作品
in their off-off-off broadway production
契科夫的《普拉托诺夫》
of Chekhov's 'Platonov.'"
好多个"外"啊
That's a lot of "OFF"s.
我们去那儿看看有谁知道他在做什么
Let's see if anyone down there knows what he was into.
这真是糟透了
This is the absolute end.
那边发生了什么事
What's going on out there?
奥西普已被村民们处以私刑
Osip's been lynched by the villagers.
抱歉  排练不对外公开
I'm sorry. This is a closed rehearsal.
纽约警局  我是贝克特探长
NYPD. I'm detective Beckett.
我们为贾斯汀·马奎特而来
We're here about Justin Marquette.
贾斯汀怎么了  他没事吧
What about Justin? Is he okay?
我们是通过戏剧公司认识的
We met through the theater company
三个月前开始交往
and started dating three months ago.
他今天没来排练
I knew something was wrong
我就觉得会不会是出事了
when he didn't show up for rehearsal today.
你最后一次见到他是什么时候
And when was the last time you saw him?
昨天早上  在我那里
Yesterday morning at my place.
我们出去晨跑了
We, um... we went for a run,
然后他冲了澡之后就去上班了
and then he showered and left for work.
他在哪上班
Where did he work?
大多数时候是做临时工
Temp jobs, mostly.
他最近挣的不多
He wasn't getting much recently,
但他说他不在乎  因为...
but he said that he didn't mind, because...
这样他就有更多时间和我在一起了
because it gave him more time to spend with me.
知道他昨晚去最佳旅伴酒店
Any idea what he would be doing at the
干什么吗
Best Traveler Hotel last night?
不知道  酒店
No -- uh, hotel?
他在酒店吗
He was -- he was at a hotel?
劳拉  我知道这很难
Look, Laura, I know this is difficult,
但贾斯汀是不是有可能在劈腿
but is it possible that Justin was seeing someone else?
什么  不会的
What? No.
他有没有牵扯上什么危险或违法的事
Was he involved in anything dangerous or illegal?
不不  据我所知  没有
No, not -- not that I know of. No.
他认识的人之中
Was there anyone in his life
有谁想要伤害他吗
that might have wanted to harm him?
前几天的那件事  记得吗
There was that thing the other day, remember?
什么事
What thing?
一个疯女人在街上走过来
Some crazy woman walked up to him on the street
威胁他
and threatened him.
对  贾斯汀都吓坏了
That's right. Justin was totally rattled.
晚上差点不能上台表演
He could barely perform that night.
-他知道她是谁吗  -不知道
- Did he know who she was? - Mnh-mnh.
他也不想谈起那件事
And he did not want to talk about it, either.
他只说事情发生在第九大道和梅瑟街的
All he said was that it happened outside a coffee shop
咖啡店外
on 9th and Mercer.
谢谢
Thanks.
咖啡店打来的
That was the coffee shop.
一位咖啡师目击了全过程
A barista saw the whole thing go down.
店外的一个女人走向贾斯汀
A woman walked up to Justin outside
开始朝他吼
and started yelling at him.
-知道长相了吗  -还不止呢
- You get a description? - I did better than that.
那女人是常客了
The woman's a regular customer.
她有一张会员卡  名字叫安妮塔·米勒
She's got a loyalty card, and her name's Anita Miller.
-我派人去带她来  -好的
- I'll send a unit to pick her up. - Great.
感谢前来  米勒女士
Thanks for coming in, Ms. Miller.
我是贝克特探长
I'm detective Beckett.
我想问你几个问题  关于...
Uh, I just need to ask you a few questions about --
贾斯汀·马奎特
Justin Marquette.
看来你认识他
So you know him.
不止是认识了  探长
I more than know him, detective.
事实上  我杀了他
In fact... I killed him.
你是在认罪吗
Are you confessing?
给我点纸  我把一切都写下来
Just give me some paper. I want to write it all down.
好的
Yeah.
11秒认罪
11 seconds to a confession.
一定是你的最佳战绩了
That's got to be your personal best.
听起来你很失望啊  卡塞尔
You sound like you're disappointed, Castle.
是的  有点失望
Well, I am, a little.
秘密电话  147号房
I mean, a secret phone, room 147 --
这个案子很有阴谋的潜质
this case had conspiratorial promise.
更有可能的是贾斯汀
Well, most likely Justin
背着女友跟安妮塔好了
was cheating on his girlfriend with Anita,
后来两人在酒店见面
and the two of them met up at the hotel,
于是场面就失控了
and that's where things went south.
很可能就是这样  真无聊
Yes, well, most likely, that is boring.
并不是每个案子都会被神秘和阴谋笼罩的
Look, not every case has to be shrouded in mystery and intrigue.
有麻烦了
Yo. Uh, we got a problem.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我查了安妮塔·米勒的行踪
Well, I was looking into Anita Miller's whereabouts
想把她和酒店联系起来
to try to tie her to the hotel,
但她的信用卡记录显示
except her credit-card records
她昨晚在法吉奥饭店
show that she was at Le Fagio restaurant last night.
可能是别人刷了她的信用卡
So maybe someone else used her credit card.
不  经理确认是她本人
Nah. The manager I.D.'d her.
他说她和另一个人平摊了饭钱
And he said that she split the bill with another guy,
是她的戒酒担保人
Her A.A. Sponsor.
我刚问过他  他证实
I just spoke to him, and he confirmed
他们从晚上9点半到零点半都在一起
that they were together from 9:30 P.M. To 12:30 A.M.
正好在案发时间范围内
But that's our entire time-of-death window.
如果属实  那么安妮塔不可能是凶手
If that's true, then Anita can't be our killer.
那她为什么要认罪
Then why is she confessing?
看来也不那么无聊
Not so boring after all.
安妮塔·米勒承认自己是凶手
So, Anita Miller is confessing to the murder,
但她有不在场证明
and she has an alibi.
我们还在继续调查  长官
Yeah, we're still trying to make sense of it, sir.
会不会是死亡时间判断错误了
Is it possible that we misjudged the time of death?
不  蕾妮确信自己的检测
No. No, Lanie stands behind her examination.
好的  那么不在场证明呢
Okay, then, what about the alibi?
埃斯波西托已经和餐厅的人证实过了
Esposito verified it with the restaurant.
餐厅经理  迎宾员  甚至服务生
The manager, the hostess, even the waiter
都确认安妮塔整个晚上都在那儿
confirmed that Anita was there all evening.
不仅如此  而且这家餐厅离酒店很远
Not only that, but this restaurant is nowhere near the hotel.
那她就不可能是凶手
Then she couldn't have killed the victim,
那就查清楚她为什么撒谎
so find out why she's lying.
写好了  我记得的所有事都写在上面了
It's all there, everything I remember about what I did.
我们只是想当面再确认一遍
Well, we just wanted to go over this in person,
避免供词前后有出入
just to clear up any discrepancies.
什么前后出入
What discrepancies?
你就告诉我们发生了什么事
Well, why don't you just tell us what happened?
我去他的房间见他
Well, I went to see him in his room.
-哪间房间  -147号房
- Which room was that? - Room 147.
147号房
Room 147?
就在最佳伴旅酒店
At the Best Traveler Hotel.
我敲了门
I knocked on the door.
他立马就开门了
He opened it almost immediately.
恭候你多时了  进来吧
Been waiting for you. Come on in.
给你拿点水喝
Let me get you a water.
他说要给我一瓶水
He offered me a bottle of water,
然后走到迷你冰箱去拿
and then he went to the mini-fridge.
就在这时我掏出了枪
That's when I took out the gun.
他转过身要把水递给我  然后我
He turned around to give me the water, and I...
我向他开枪了
I shot him.
我往他胸口开了一枪
I shot him in the chest.
之后发生了什么
And then what happened?
他看上去很惊讶
He looked surprised.
摇摇晃晃向后退
He staggered back.
手上的水掉在地上
He dropped the bottle of water,
他用手抓住了背后的椅子
and he kind of gripped onto the back of this chair.
然后他倒了下去  椅子也被带倒了
Then he fell and knocked it over.
她描述的和犯罪现场一模一样
That's exactly how we found the crime scene.
她肯定去过那儿
She must've been there.
怎么会  她怎么可能去过
How? How is that possible?
安妮塔  你和贾斯汀·马奎特什么关系
Anita, what was your relationship with Justin Marquette?
我和他的关系
My relationship?
你们两个很熟吗
Were the two of you involved?
我想没有
Uh, I don't think so.
那你怎么认识他的
Then how did you know him?
我也不确定
I'm not sure.
如果你不知道自己是怎么认识他的
If you don't know how you knew him,
那你为什么杀他呢
then why would you kill him?
我有酒瘾
I'm an alcoholic.
他为我的酗酒负责
He was responsible for my drinking.
这怎么说
How was he responsible?
我不知道  我很抱歉
I don't know. I'm -- I'm sorry.
我最近一直都很混乱
I've been really confused lately.
因为酗酒的事
Because of the drinking.
不  我已经戒酒戒了四年
No, I've been sober for four years.
我依旧在和酒瘾作斗争
I mean, god knows I still struggle,
但是过去的这两个礼拜
but these last two weeks,
我的记忆非常的模糊
they've just been really... blurry.
你记得你昨晚和你的担保人去吃晚饭吗
Do you remember going to dinner with your sponsor last night?
-是昨天晚上吗  -是的
- Was that last night? - Mm-hmm.
是的  没错  是昨天晚上
Yes, you're right. It was.
那么  你什么时候去酒店见贾斯汀呢
So, then, when did you go to the hotel and meet Justin?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
安妮塔  大概几天前  有目击证人
Anita, we have a witness that saw you accost Justin
在咖啡店外看见你和贾斯汀起冲突
outside of a coffee shop a couple of days ago.
-你记得吗  -是的  我记得
- Do you remember that? - Yes, I do.
他当时在和一个大块头的秃顶男人说话
Uh, he was talking to this big, bald man.
我得警告贾斯汀  告诉他他有危险
I had to warn Justin, to tell him he was in danger.
-那个秃顶男人要害他  -不  是我
- From the bald man. - No, from me.
我见到贾斯汀时
The moment I saw Justin,
我就有一种我会伤害他的不祥预感
I just had this awful feeling that I was gonna hurt him.
而且我真的这么做了
And I did.
好的  谢谢
All right. Thanks.
昨晚酒店没人看到安妮塔
So -- no one at the hotel saw Anita last night,
而且技术部在监控录像上也完全找不到她
and tech can't find her in any of the security-cam footage.
这一点也说通
This doesn't make any sense.
她知道案发的细节
She knows details about our crime
这些细节只有凶手才知道
that only our killer could know.
法医那边怎么样  鉴证组那边有没有发现什么
What about forensics? Did CSU come up with anything?
在纽约的酒店房间能有什么发现
In a hotel room in New York city?
发现的都是情趣之物
They found all kinds of fun stuff,
但没发现任何安妮塔和147号房的联系
but nothing that tied Anita back to room 147.
也许这是一出戏
You know, maybe it's an act,
障眼法之类的
you know, some kind of smokescreen,
她想要替别人背黑锅
and she's taking the fall for someone else.
可她一定知道我们会查证她的不在场证明
Except she had to have known that we would check her alibi,
而这与她的招供完全相悖
Which completely contradicts her confession.
好了  说吧
All right. Come on.
啥
Hmm?
跟我们说说你的"高见"  老兄
Give us one of your theories, bro.
说吧  不管你说什么  都不可能
Come on. And whatever it is, it can't be any crazier
比现在的情况更不可思议
than what we're already dealing with.
好的
Okay.
我觉得
I think...
不得不承认  我现在完全高见无能
I'm man enough to admit I'm completely theory-less.
也许安妮塔受到了什么精神伤害
Maybe Anita suffered some kind of psychotic break.
我已经叫了人给她做精神评估
I've ordered a psych eval,
但是精神病也解释不了
but psychosis doesn't explain
她是怎么知道谋杀案的细节的
How she knew all about the murder.
或者她为什么要杀他
Or why she killed the guy in the first place.
我反复查过她的通话记录
I double-checked her phone records.
她和贾斯汀·马奎特并没有
There's not a single call or text
任何的通话或者短信往来
between her and Justin Marquette.
看上去他们两个之前根本不认识对方
It's like they had no history at all.
好的  你们两个去她的住处
Okay, why don't you guys go over to her apartment
核查她的电子邮件  日程表  日记
and check everything -- e-mails, calendars, her diary --
看看是否能发现什么
And let's see if we can find anything there
把她和被害人联系在一起
that'll connect her to our victim.
马上去办
We're on it.
贝克特探长  卡塞尔先生  很高兴见到你们
Detective Beckett, Mr. Castle, good to see you.
霍洛维医生  多谢你跑一趟
Thank you so much for coming in, Dr. Holloway.
你们这儿有位病人在等我吧
I gather you have a patient for me.
没错
Oh, yeah.
我们搜遍了这房子的所有房间
Well, we've been through every room in the house.
没发现枪和沾血衣物
No gun, no bloody clothes,
找不到证据把安妮塔和凶杀现场或贾斯汀联系起来
Nothing that links Anita back to that crime scene or to Justin.
是没找到  但你来看她的日程表
Maybe not, but check out her date book.
有几页被撕掉了
Some pages have been ripped out,
过去两周的日程记录都没了
including all of the last two weeks.
-两周吗  等等  -没错
- Two weeks? Wait a minute. - Yeah.
安妮塔说过她过去两周一直很"迷糊"
That's how long Anita says she's been feeling "Blurry."
也许她电脑里也有日程表备份
Maybe she kept a calendar on her computer.
看  她确实备份了
Yeah, looks like she did,
但过去两周的记录也被抹掉了
but the same two weeks have been erased.
看起来有人想掩盖什么
Seems like someone's trying to cover something up.
是谁呢  想掩盖什么
Yeah, but who? And what?
尽管我也喜欢身陷谜局
As much as I love a good mystery,
但我还是有点希望他能让我们弄清楚
a small part of me is hoping he can give us some clarity
这到底是怎么回事
on what the hell is going on.
说到弄清楚  你说
Uh, speaking of clarity, what did you mean
阿丽克西斯可能因为其它事情
when you said that there might be something else
不搬回你的公寓  是指什么事
that's keeping alexis from moving back to your loft?
我也不知道
I don't know!
阿丽克西斯不肯讲  我想...
And Alexis won't talk about it, so...
或许等霍洛维医生和安妮塔谈完
maybe when Dr. Holloway's done talking to Anita,
可以让他和阿丽克西斯去聊聊
I can get him to talk to Alexis.
医生  你的判断如何
Hey. So, what's the verdict?
目前  据我观察
Based on my examination so far,
她精神状态正常  但有些混乱
I find her to be mentally competent, if somewhat disoriented.
从所有迹象来看  她似乎讲的是实话
By all indications, she seems to be telling the truth.
就是说她确实杀了贾斯汀·马奎特
Meaning she did kill Justin Marquette?
要不就是她深信是她杀的
Or she believes she did, anyway.
那混乱呢
And what about the disorientation?
是怎么导致的
How do you account for that?
可能是身体或神经问题
Could be medical or a neurologic condition,
或者是对药物的不良反应
adverse reaction to drugs.
可能她经历了创伤性事件
It's possible she experienced a traumatic event
导致了逆行性遗忘
which caused some sort of retrograde amnesia.
像杀人这样的创伤性事件吗
So, traumatic like killing someone?
有可能  我会做个详细检查
Potentially. I'm gonna do a full work-up.
结论出来才会知道更多
I'll know more when the results come back.
谢谢你  医生
Thank you, doctor.
安妮塔·米勒深信她杀了死者
So, Anita Miller believes she killed the victim,
但事实证明不可能是她
but the facts say she couldn't have.
不  不是所有的事实
No, not all the facts.
我们知道她在咖啡店外和贾斯汀搭话
I mean, we know she accosted Justin outside the coffee shop,
她供认了谋杀罪行
she confessed to the murder,
而且她十分清楚谋杀过程
and she has intimate knowledge of the crime.
很显然  我们现在还没办法解释一切  但
So, look. Clearly, we haven't explained everything, but --
但你认为她是凶手
But you believe she killed him.
我认为除非事态有变
I think that until something changes,
否则她有最大嫌疑
she's our best suspect.
警探  你得和这人谈谈
Detective, there's someone here you need to talk to.
这是萨姆·卡森
This is Sam Carson.
把你对我讲的跟她说一遍
Tell her what you told me.
我想供认一起谋杀案
I want to confess to a murder.
我杀了贾斯汀·马奎特
I killed Justin Marquette.
我想事态有变了
I'd say something just changed.
对  是我
Yeah, it was me.
别误会  我并不是以此为荣
Don't get me wrong -- it's not like I'm proud of it.
我没听错吧
Did I hear right?
又有人供认谋杀吗
Another person has confessed to this murder?
对  但我觉得他只是想引人注意罢了
Yeah, but I just think he's some kind of attention-seeker.
对  到目前为止  他的供述
Yeah -- so far, the confession
只是重复了新闻报道的内容
is just a rehash of the news report.
卡森先生  你知道
Mr. Carson, do you realize
对警察做假口供是犯法的吗
that making false statements to the police is a crime?
我说的是实话
I'm telling you the truth.
我在酒店房间杀了个人
I killed the guy in his hotel room.
好吧  那是哪个房间
Okay, fine. What room was that?
147  是147房间
147. It was room 147.
你得告诉我到底发生了什么
I need you to tell me exactly what happened.
我在他房间
I was in his room, uh --
不  我要知道细节
No, no. I need details.
你躲在壁橱里吗  踢开了门吗
Were you hiding in the closet? Did you kick down the door?
不  我敲门的
No. I knocked.
恭候你多时了  进来吧
Been waiting for you. Come on in.
给你拿点水喝
Let me get you a water.
他让我进去了  给我拿了水
He let me in, offered me a water.
拿了水
A water?
对  一瓶水
Yeah, like, a bottle.
然后他去了冰箱那儿
Then he -- he went to the fridge.
就是那时我掏出了枪
That's when I pulled out my gun.
他转过身来后  我朝他开了枪
He turned around, and I shot him...
正中胸口
Right in the chest.
然后呢
And then what?
他向后倒去  抓住了椅子
He fell back, grabbed for a chair,
倒下的时候把椅子也带倒了
Knocked it over when he fell down.
然后我就走了
Then I left.
你为什么杀他
Why did you kill him?
为什么
Why?
对啊
Yeah.
因为我很愤怒
'cause I was angry.
我有情绪问题  你懂吧
I got anger issues, you know?
我看到他的时候  就满腔怒火
And when I saw him, I was just so filled with rage.
是因为他对你做了什么
Because he did what to you?
这个  我也没弄明白
That's -- that's the part I'm not too clear on.
前几个星期的事我都记不大清了
The last -- last couple of weeks have been just kind of hazy.
你怎么认识死者的
How did you know the victim?
我没印象我认识他
I don't -- I don't know that I do.
那么  他让你十分愤怒  但你根本不认识他吗
Okay. He filled you with rage, and you don't know him?
那你为什么要去147号房间呢
Why did you go to Room147 in the first place?
-是他联系你的吗  -我忘记了
- Did he contact you? - I don't remember.
你怎么能忘记了呢
How do you not remember?
你在耍什么把戏呢
What kind of game are you playing here?
我没有在耍任何把戏
I'm not playing any game!
你知道我认为你在干什么吗
You know what I think you're doing?
你在阻挠我办案
You're trying to sabotage my case!
你知道没有检察官会在
You know that no D.A. is going to get a conviction
多人供认情况下定罪
with multiple confessions!
多人供认
Multiple confessions?
没错  你和安妮塔·米勒一起策划的
Yeah, you and Anita Miller are working together on this.
你们要不是互相为对方掩盖罪行
You're either covering for each other,
就是一起为其他人掩盖罪行
or you're covering for someone else out there.
谁是安妮塔·米勒
Who the hell is Anita Miller?
你知道她是谁
You know who she is.
我从没见过这个女人
I've never seen that woman before in my life.
我不认识他
I'm telling you, I don't know him.
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
因为萨姆跟你讲的案发情况一模一样
Because Sam told us the same story you did,
不同的是是他杀了贾斯汀
But that he killed Justin.
他在撒谎  我杀了贾斯汀·马奎特
Well, he's lying. I killed Justin Marquette.
我们没找到萨姆和安妮塔之间的关联
So, we can't find a link between Sam and Anita,
也没找到他们俩和死者之间的关联
or between either one of them and our victim.
那萨姆的不在场证明呢
What about Sam's alibi?
他的弟弟说他和萨姆
His brother says that he and Sam
昨晚一整晚都在棒球室内练习场
were at the batting cages all last night.
而且根据监控录像来看
And based on the security video,
萨姆根本没去过酒店
Sam never set foot in the hotel.
他们俩都坚信是自己杀了贾斯汀
They both believe they killed Justin,
他们俩都清楚谋杀的细节
They both know details about the murder,
而且他们俩都拥有相同的记忆问题
and they both have similar memory problems.
这其中必有关联
I mean, they must be connected.
假如是他们的生活确有交集  只不过不是
What if their lives intersect, just not in such a...
一般的那种交集呢
literal sense?
不要说  卡塞尔  求你了
No. Castle, no. Please.
如果你又要说平行宇宙理论
If this is some alternate-universe theory,
我可没心情听
I'm not in the mood.
真的吗
Really?
平行宇宙  你也太小瞧我了
Alternate universe -- that's how little you think of me.
对不起  对不起
I'm sorry. I'm -- I'm sorry.
我只是  我以为你要
I just -- I thought that you --
不是  他们俩是心灵相通的
No, they're psychically linked.
而且不是彼此相通  而是和真正的凶手相通
And not just to each other, but to the actual killer.
他们是通过他或她的眼看到了犯罪过程
See, they're seeing the crime through his or her eyes.
这种感觉实在是太身临其境了
And the experience is so visceral
以至于让萨姆和安妮塔
that both Sam and Anita
都认为他们自己才是杀人凶手
think that they committed the crime themselves.
对不起  我只是  你兴奋了
I'm sorry. It's just, you got excited.
-看起来有点可爱  -是是
- It's kind of cute. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你知道我有多喜欢奇怪的事情
You know how I like the weird stuff.
谁的短信
Who's that?
没人  没什么事
Oh, uh, it's nobody. Nothing.
没什么事
It's -- it's nothing.
警探
Detective?
又来了一个
We got another one.
又一个什么
Another what?
我叫德怀特·卡瑟斯  是注册会计师
I'm Dwight Carruthers, cpa.
我来自首
I'm here to turn myself in...
我杀害了贾斯汀·马奎特
...for killing Justin Marquette.
-不会吧  -好了
- No. - All right.
这个案子现在正式  无与伦比了
This is now officially...outstanding.
你们要来看看这个
Hey. You guys need to see this.
等等  我需要供认
Wait, I-I need to confess.
是嘛  排队去吧
Yeah, take a number.
一旦我们意识到有可能
Once we realized that someone
有人去过安妮塔的公寓
might've gone through Anita's apartment,
我们让警员排查了那一块区域
We had UNIs canvass the area.
安妮塔的一个邻居记得两周前
Now, one of Anita's neighbors remembers seeing a red van
看到过一辆红色货车停在她家门口
parked outside her place about two weeks ago.
就是从那时起她开始感觉意识混乱的
Right when she started feeling disoriented.
是的  不止如此  我们问过萨姆·卡森的邻居
Yeah, not only that, we checked in with Sam Carson's neighbors.
结果发现其中一个人也记得几天后
Turns out, one of them remembers seeing the same red van
看到过一辆相同的红色货车停在卡森家外
parked outside of Carson's house a few nights later.
她之所以记得是因为他觉得货车看起来很可疑
She remembers it because she thought it looked suspicious.
你知道车牌号吗
Did you get a plate number?
不知道  但她用她的手机照了一张相
No, but she took a picture with her phone.
看看谁在驾驶
Take a look who's behind the wheel.
这不是
Is that...
一个大块头秃顶男人
A big, bald man,
就跟安妮塔声称她看见
just like the one Anita said she saw
和死者在咖啡店外交谈的人一样
talking to our victim outside the coffee shop.
那么死者和两个嫌疑犯之间
So our victim and two suspects
的确是有关联之处的
do have something in common.
没错  就是他
Yeah -- him.
-那么现在有三个人自首了  -是的  长官
- So, now there are three of them. - Yes, sir.
但是我们相信这个男人就是案子的关键
But we believe that this man is the key to our case.
他的货车分别在安妮塔和萨姆的公寓外被人看到过
His van was seen outside both Anita and Sam's apartments,
并且安妮塔认出他是
And Anita I.D.'d him as the guy
和死者在咖啡店外交谈的那个人
that was talking to our victim outside the coffee shop.
这个男人和卡瑟斯先生有什么关系
And what is this man's connection to Mr. Carruthers?
这就是我要去查明的
That's what I'm gonna find out.
我已经准备好了负全部责任
I-I'm prepared to take full responsibility
并对自己所做的一切供认不讳
and admit to what I did.
我相信  你认识这个男人吗
Yes, I'm sure you are. Now, do you recognize this man?
你不想听我的供述吗
Don't you want to hear my confession?
最佳旅伴酒店  147号房间
Best traveler hotel, room 147,
贾斯汀给了你一瓶水  你一枪打死了他
Justin offered you water, and then you shot him.
你是怎么知道的
How -- how did you know?
贝克特  这跟安妮塔画的一样
Beckett? Just like the one Anita drew.
德怀特  这个符号是什么意义
Dwight, what does that symbol mean?
我不知道
I -- uh, uh, I don't -- I don't know.
它最近一直浮现在我的脑海里
It's just been stuck in my head lately.
但是就算知道又能怎么样呢
But what difference does that make?
-我枪杀了一个人  -我们知道
- I-I shot a guy! - We know.
你能仔细看看这些照片吗
Now, can you take a close look at these pictures
告诉我们你见过这个男人吗
And tell me if you recognize that man?
没有  但是货车看起来很熟悉
Uh...no, but the van looks familiar.
你以前见过吗  哪里见到的
You've seen it before? Where?
我不是很清楚
Uh, I'm not sure.
最近有点
I've -- I've been --
稀里糊涂的  就这最近两周
Confused recently, like the last two weeks?
德怀特  认真想  这很重要
Dwight, think. This is important.
那  那是上周二  大约中午
It -- it was last tuesday... a-around noon.
我从自信训练班回家
I was coming home from... assertiveness training,
那辆货车停在豪士顿街上
And -- and that van was parked on Houston Street
就在我公寓外面
outside my apartment.
豪士顿街上有交通摄像头
There are traffic cams on Houston.
说不定拍到了车牌号
They might've caught a plate number.
你们不是吧
Um...seriously?
我杀了人  你们却只关心货车
I killed someone, and all you care about is a van?
技术人员搜索了上周二以来豪士顿街
All right. Techs scrubbed traffic cam footage
交通摄像头拍下的影像资料
from last tuesday on Houston.
他们找到了我们要找的车辆
They got a hit on our vehicle.
被注册在迈尔斯·马德森的名下
It's registered to a Miles Madsen.
太好了  那就是我们要找的人
Great. That's our guy.
我们还知道他什么
So, what do we know about him?
他在逃  警员搜查了他的公寓
That he's in the wind -- uniforms hit his apartment,
可房东说已经好几周没见过马德森了
but the landlord said he hasn't seen Madsen in weeks.
好吧  发全面通缉
Okay, put out an APB.
尽可能找出所有与他相关的信息
Find out everything you can about him.
现在  他是将这些人连在一起的唯一一环
Right now, he's the only link connecting all these people.
你要去哪里
Where you going?
我有些事情要做
Uh, I've got an errand to run.
你能跟卡塞尔说我一小时后就回来吗
Can you tell castle that I'll be back in an hour?
-没问题  -多谢
- Yeah. - Thanks.
谢谢你能来见我
Thanks for meeting with me.
没事  什么事情那么重要
Yeah. What's so important?
你知道你和你爸之间的事
You know that I don't take sides
我不会偏袒任何一个  对吧
on anything between you and your dad, right?
我知道  我很感谢
Yeah. I appreciate that.
是这样的
Okay, well...
你爸爸想让你搬回来住
Your dad wants you to move back home.
我知道你说你租房合同还没到期
And I know that you said you have a lease,
可你又说你还有些其他原因
but you also said that there were other reasons
你为什么不想搬回来呢  我只是
why you didn't want to move back, and I-I just...
想确认你不想回来的原因不是我
I want to make sure that one of those reasons isn't me.
不
Oh, no.
不不  完全不是因为你
No, no, it's -- it's not you at all.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
因为我最不愿意见到的就是
'cause the last thing I want to do
我让你在你自己家感到不受欢迎
is make you feel unwelcome in your own home.
不是因为你  是因为我自己
No, it's... not you, it's me.
我搬出去时  我爸对我说的那些话
All those things my dad said when I was moving out --
说我搬出去和男友住是错误的决定
About me making a mistake moving in with my boyfriend --
他说的对
He was right.
我现在全都明白了
I can see it so clearly now.
为什么那时就不明白呢
Why didn't I then?
你那时身处爱情迷雾之中
You were in the love haze.
爱情迷雾
The love haze?
爱情就像毒品
It's like a drug!
会让聪明人做出愚蠢的事情
It makes intelligent people do stupid things.
当迷雾都散开  你瞧瞧周围
Then it clears, and you look around,
你便会想  我这之前怎么想的
and you wonder, "What was I thinking?"
你爸爸只是想帮助你
Your dad just wants to help.
应该让他出手相助
It's okay to let him.
是的  不过这是我犯的错误
Yes, but this was my mistake.
他不应该为此埋单
He shouldn't have to pay for it,
我要继续兼职家教
so I will tutor
尽我所能直到合同结束
and do whatever I have to until the lease is up.
好吧
Okay.
我明白  听我说
I get it. Look.
你做的这些看似很高尚  可惜不是
I know what you're doing seems noble, but it's not.
长时间的工作  精疲力竭
I mean, the long hours, the exhaustion --
你这么做其实是惩罚自己
What you're actually doing is punishing yourself.
相信我  我曾和你处境一样
Trust me. I've been there.
这没有必要
This -- this isn't necessary.
你爸爸很爱你
Your dad loves you.
他很担心你
He worries about you.
你的悔过已经足够了
I think your penance is paid.
抱歉  我得走了
I'm sorry. I have to go.
考虑下  好吗
Uh, just think about it, okay?
回见
I'll see you.
你们找到马德森了吗
Hey, did you guys find Madsen?
没有  不过就快了
No, but we're getting close.
我们发现他是阿波罗尖峰公司的
We figured out that he's an independent contractor
独立承包人
for Apollo Pinnacle, Inc.,
这家公司是
which turns out to be a front
永恒视野组织的幌子公司
for another organization called E.H.I.,
全称是永恒视野研究所
or Eternal Horizons Institute.
那是什么
And what is that?
引用他们网站的原话
Well, to quote their website,
"该研究所提供庇护  启蒙
"E.H.I. provides sanctuary, enlightenment,
以及通向终极自我的道路"
and pathways to the ultimate self."
他们声称在全球范围内有上千名追随者
They claim to have thousands of followers all over the world.
不过不是所有人都满意他们的服务
But not all of them are satisfied customers.
在2005年  三名追随者
In 2005, three of those followers died
死于某种蒸汗屋入会仪式
in some kind of sweat-lodge initiation.
虽然该组织遭到起诉
Charges were filed, but, ultimately,
但最终法院还是裁定属于意外死亡
the deaths were ruled accidental.
追随者  入会仪式  听起来像是邪教
Followers? Initiations? This thing sounds like a cult.
是个邪教
Oh, it's a cult, all right,
有个富有魅力又阴险狡诈的领袖
complete with charismatic and sinister leader,
给你看看他们的招募视频
brought to you courtesy of this recruitment video.
大家好  欢迎各位
Hello, and welcome.
我是古斯塔沃·鲍尔博士
My name is Dr. Gustavo Bauer,
永恒视野研究所的创始人
founder of the Eternal Horizons Institute.
古斯塔沃·鲍尔博士  哪个领域的博士
Dr. Gustavo Bauer? So, what is he a doctor of?
这里说他有一个超人格心理学博士学位
Says here he holds a PhD in trans-personal psychology.
一个从没听说过的大学颁发的
From never-heard-of-it university.
生物认知项目来帮助你解放自我
...bio-cognitive program to help free you
将自己从不良情绪中解放出来
from the negative anchors holding you down
从而展翅高飞
so you can soar.
快来我们
Visit us at one of
永恒视野研究所的接待处
the Eternal Horizon Institute's many reception centers
勇敢迈出第一步
and take the first step
发掘真正的自我
at becoming the person you were truly meant to be.
看好了
Wait for it.
那是安妮塔和德怀特画过的标志
That's the symbol that Anita and Dwight were drawing.
没错  他们确认过  萨姆也画过这标志
Yes, and the boys checked. Sam's been drawing it, as well.
也就是说  他们三个
Okay, so, the three of them
肯定都参加了这个组织
must have been a part of whatever the hell this thing is.
这就是联系
That's our connection.
只不过我们分别问过  他们都否认了
Except we asked each of them. They all denied being members.
可他们还承认了杀害贾斯汀·马奎特呢
Yeah, but they also said that they killed Justin Marquette,
而我们知道那是假话
and we know that that's not true, either.
上哪找这个永恒视野去
So, where is this E.H.I.?
就在市里  中城区
Right here in the city -- midtown.
这案子远超我标准很高的期待值
This case is exceeding even my lofty expectations.
一场不可能谋杀
An impossible murder
牵扯到一个若有若无  神秘莫测的邪教
connected to a shadowy and mysterious cult.
更别提多金了
Not to mention prosperous.
这可是曼哈顿区最好的房产
This is prime Manhattan real estate.
你好  我们来见鲍尔博士
Hi. We're here to see Dr. Bauer.
-我是  -您是贝克特探长
- I'm -- - Detective Beckett.
而您是理查德·卡塞尔
Richard Castle.
欢迎来到永恒视野
Welcome to E.H.I.
鲍尔博士在恭候两位
Dr. Bauer's expecting you.
怎么恭候  我们又没预约
How? We didn't make an appointment.
鲍尔博士天赋异禀
Dr. Bauer's a brilliant man.
请这边走
Right this way.
他就在里面
He's just inside.
那个
Yeah, uh...
他不在啊
No, he's not!
此言差矣
On the contrary.
老大哥范儿十足啊
That is so...big brother.
你们好  贝克特探长  卡塞尔先生
Greetings, Detective Beckett, Mr. Castle.
两位有何贵干
What can I do for you?
那得麻烦你和我们面谈了
Well, uh, you could start by speaking to us in person.
非常遗憾  我在斯德哥尔摩参加一场研讨会
Regrettably, I'm in Stockholm, conducting a seminar.
那好吧
Okay. Well, then...
你认识这个人吗  贾斯汀·马奎特
Do you know this man, Justin Marquette?
恐怕不认识
I'm afraid not.
那这个人呢  迈尔斯·马德森
What about this man, Miles Madsen?
我知道他为你工作
I understand he works for you.
马德森先生不为永恒视野工作已有段时间了
Mr. Madsen has not been employed by E.H.I. for some time --
准确地说  有些年了
Years, in fact.
马德森受雇于你时工作内容是什么
Well, what did mr. Madsen do when he worked for you?
鉴于他已不再受雇于我
Since he is no longer in my employ,
我不知问这个有何关联
I don't see the relevance.
关系就在于
The relevance
他牵涉进了一桩凶杀案
Is that he is connected to a murder investigation.
你浓厚的敌意令我震惊  探长
I'm struck by the level of your hostility, Detective.
这不利健康
It's not healthy.
一名凶杀组探长询问你雇员的情况
You know what I'm struck by is your total lack of curiosity
你却毫不忧心  这才叫人震惊呢
as to why a homicide detective is asking about your employee.
是前雇员
Former employee.
随便他是什么  总之他与这个案子有牵连
Well, whatever he is, he is definitely involved in this case,
此外还牵涉到三人  都是你这个小组的
along with three other members of your...little group --
安妮塔·米勒  萨姆·卡森  德怀特·卡瑟斯
Anita Miller, Sam Carson, Dwight Carruthers.
抱歉  探长
I'm sorry, Detective.
这些人不是永恒视野的成员
Those people are not part of E.H.I.
这真是
Wow. That's...
你查都不查就知道
amazing how you would just know that
还真让人惊奇
off the top of your head.
我亲自接见本组织每个成员
I make a point of meeting every member of my E.H.I. family.
你提到的这三位不在其中
The people you mentioned are not among them.
那想必你不会介意
Well, then, I'm sure you won't mind
我们搜查下你的档案
if we check your files,
以及你存有的迈尔斯·马德森的文件
along with the records that you have on Miles Madsen.
那你就需要搜查令了  探长
You'd need a warrant for that, Detective,
但你申请不到的
and you won't get one.
怎么了
What's that?
他们准备好了
They're ready.
真抱歉  研讨会要开始了
I'm sorry. My session is starting.
贾思敏会送两位离开
Jasmine will show you out.
等下  鲍尔博士  我
No. Dr. Bauer, I -- uh --
这边请
Right this way.
让鲍尔说着了
Bauer was right.
法官不肯签发搜查令
The judge turned us down for a search warrant.
你真以为永恒天视野的"大教主"是背后主谋
You really think E.H.I.'s grand pooh-bah is behind this?
我认为他知道马德森在哪
I think that he knows where Madsen is
而且马德森还在替他卖命
and that Madsen is still working for him.
做什么呢
But doing what?
而这种种又和
And what does any of this have to do
落魄演员贾斯汀·马奎特有什么关系
with a struggling actor like Justin Marquette?
-哈  -"哈"什么
- Huh. - "Huh" what?
永恒视野官网
Uh, the E.H.I. website --
简介里说他们设有各种课程
the testimonials claim that they have programs
以帮助人们戒烟  戒酒  以及
that help people quit smoking, quit drinking, uh,
重新掌控生活
take charge of their lives.
所以呢
So?
这三个自首的人
So, all three of our confessors
全都有这类问题  酗酒
have had problems in their lives -- uh, alcoholism,
暴躁易怒  缺乏自信
anger management, assertiveness issues --
而他们都有可能找永恒视野寻求帮助
all things that they could've gone through E.H.I. to treat.
但他们都予以否认了
But they all claim that they didn't.
如果他们找过呢
But what if they did?
如果他们找过
What if they did,
但出于某种原因  永恒视野想要消除所有
but something made E.H.I. want to eliminate
与自身有关联的线索呢
any record of their involvement?
撕掉日记本的相关内容  删除日历记录
Torn date-book pages, wiped calendars.
也许这就是马德森去他们住所的原因
Maybe that's why Madsen went to their apartments --
去消除所有能联系到永恒视野的证据
To erase any trace of their connection to E.H.I.
卡塞尔  仅仅删掉日程记录是不够的
Castle, you can't just do that by wiping out calendars.
-你还得  -消除记忆
- You'd have to -- - Wipe memories.
想想吧
Think about it.
整整两个星期模糊不清  稀里糊涂
The fogginess, the confusion over the last two weeks.
你是说  这个表面光鲜的自助组织
So y-you're saying that a glorified self-help group
能消除人的记忆吗  怎么消除
can erase people's memories? How?
用药物
With drugs.
安妮塔·米勒的检查报告出来了
Anita Miller's tests came back.
她体内普萘洛尔衍生物含量很不正常
Found unusual levels of a propranolol derivative in her system,
所以我又检查了卡森先生和卡瑟斯先生
so I tested Mr. Carson and Mr. Carruthers.
他们血液里也有这种成分
It was in their blood, as well.
普萘洛尔
Propranolol?
少量使用可以用于控制血压
In small doses, it's mainly a blood-pressure drug.
大量使用则能更改记忆
In high doses, it's been found to alter memories,
甚至消除记忆
even eliminate them.
如果它能用于更改记忆  有没有可能让人相信
If it can alter memories, could it make someone believe
他们做过一些实际上并没有做过的事呢
they had done something they actually hadn't?
正常情况下
Under normal circumstances,
人类的大脑是很容易受影响的
the human brain is very suggestible.
再加上这种药  我认为完全可能
Combined with a drug like this, I'd say it's entirely possible.
失陪
Excuse me.
太棒了
Outstanding.
这简直就是《盗梦空间》
This is straight out of "Inception."
有人把谋杀的记忆
Someone planted the memory of the murder
植入他们三人脑中
in all three of their heads,
同时让他们忘记自己和永恒视野的关系
while erasing any knowledge of their connection to E.H.I.
卡塞尔  你知道这听起来有多疯狂吗
Castle, do you have any idea how insane that sounds?
这是个阴险的计划
It's a diabolical plan.
让三个人在同一桩谋杀案上招供
Have three suspects confess to the same crime,
使警方无法逮捕其中任何一人
making it impossible for the police to arrest anyone.
但这仍无法解释他们如何在没去过现场的情况下
But none of this explains how they all knew the details
知道谋杀的细节
of the murder without actually being there.
说不定...他们去过了
Maybe...they were there,
只是...没有亲身去
just...not in person.
会不会是凶手拍摄了谋杀过程
What if justin's killer filmed the murder
然后在药物起效的时候
and then showed it to these people
播放给这些人看
while they were in their drug-induced state?
那他们就会以为这些图像
They would think the images were drawn
是他们亲身经历的
from their own experience.
如果他们看到了真正的谋杀
If they were shown the actual murder,
那他们三人就都是目击者
then that makes all three of them witnesses.
他们看到了犯罪细节
With details of the crime
或许能帮我们找到真正的凶手
that could lead to our real killer.
我告诉你  是我自己按下了扳机
I'm telling you, I pulled the trigger myself.
我也是
So did I.
听着  我知道你们都觉得这一切是真实的
Look, I understand that it seems real to you,
但可能不是真的
but it may not be.
可为什么有人要这么做
But why would somebody do this to us?
为了逃脱谋杀指控
To get away with murder.
你们只需要说出关于那个旅馆房间
We just need you to tell us everything you "remember"
你们所"记得"的一切
about being in that hotel room,
包括不经意听到的声音
Down to the last overheard whisper or --
无意中在镜子里瞥见的身影
or glimpse of a shadow in a mirror.
要记住  你们觉得不值一提的细节
Now, keep in mind that what seems like a minor detail to you
都可能会成为解决这案子的关键
may actually be the key to us solving this case.
从安妮塔开始吧
So, let's start with Anita.
我记得的第一件事是敲了147的房门
The first thing I remember is knocking on the door of 147.
过了几秒  贾斯汀开门了
After a few seconds, Justin opened it.
他笑得很轻佻  然后...
He smiled flirtatiously, and --
等一下  他没有跟我调情
Okay, he did not flirt with me.
也没跟我  他很严肃
No, he was businesslike.
你进去之后看到什么
And, uh, what did you see when you went in the room?
我记得有地毯  是米色的
I remember the carpet. It was beige.
墙纸上有隐约的花卉图案
The wallpaper had a subtle floral pattern,
冰箱上有一幅画
and there was a painting above the fridge.
我想应该是风景画
I-I think it was a landscape.
对  画的是乡村
Yeah, of a countryside.
当他从冰箱里拿出一瓶水时
And when he pulled out the bottle of water from the fridge,
我记得在冰箱侧门上
I remember there were six other bottles
还有六瓶
in the fridge door there.
不对  是五瓶  我记得很清楚
No, there were five. I remember that clear as day.
不对  是六瓶
Nuh-unh. There were six.
我也记得是五瓶
I remember five, too.
-听到了吧  -我知道自己看到了什么
- See? - I know what I saw.
你看错了
You saw wrong.
是五瓶  他看见五瓶  我也看见五瓶  你呢
There were five. He saw five. I saw five. You saw what?
卡塞尔  如果他们不能在细节上统一
Castle, if they can't agree on the details,
我觉得我们是得不到什么线索的
then I don't think we're gonna learn anything here.
恰恰相反
Au contraire.
我们刚刚知道了一个非常重要的线索
We've already learned something very, very important.
跟我来
Come with me.
去哪儿
Where we going?
回旅馆
Back to the hotel.
你们显然是在说谎  好吗
You guys are clearly lying, okay?
我...
I --
好了  卡塞尔
Come on, Castle.
能不能告诉我这是在干什么
Could you just tell me what this is all about?
等我确定自己想对了再告诉你
Not until I know I'm right.
现在我确定...
Which...
我是对的
I am.
你该知道你跟一个天才订婚了
You should know you're engaged to a genius.
对  擅长惹恼我的天才
Yes, a genius at annoying me.
现在我是贾斯汀
So, I'm Justin,
而你是其中一个向我开枪的人
and you are one of the several people who shot me.
真得有开枪的冲动唉
I'm starting to feel the urge.
我去给你拿水
I go to get you a bottle of water, and...
告诉我  你看到冰箱里有几瓶水
tell me how many bottles do you see in the fridge?
一瓶也没有  被门挡住了
None. The door's blocking it.
没错
Exactly.
这说明安妮塔  萨姆和德怀特
Which means Anita, Sam, or Dwight
也不可能看见
couldn't have seen it, either.
他们所看到的
Whatever they saw --
根本不是在这房间发生的
It didn't happen in this room!
如果他们没有目击真正的谋杀
Okay, if they didn't witness the actual murder,
那他们看到的是什么
then what did they see?
在另一个最佳旅伴旅馆的
Something that happened at another Best Traveler Hotel
另一间147号房发生的事
i-in another room 147.
我们查了附近其他分店
We checked other branches in the area.
发现三星期前
Now, three weeks ago,
长岛最佳伴旅酒店
the Best Traveler in Long Island city
把一整层都租给了永恒视野  包括147号房
rented an entire floor, including room 147, to E.H.I.
那房间和
Their room 147 is identical
我们发现被害人的房间一模一样
to the one where we found our victim.
只是冰箱门打开的方向
Except that fridge opens
和证人描述的相吻合
exactly like our witnesses described it.
永恒视野在那里做什么
What was E.H.I. Doing there?
他们跟酒店说是为了做会员活动
They told the hotel it was some kind of member event.
但是他们带了自己的保安
But they brought their own security,
并且迫使酒店工作人员离开了几个小时
and they kept hotel staff off the floor for hours.
那天确实发生了点事
Something happened that day,
与贾斯汀的谋杀案有关
something connected to Justin's murder,
他们不想有人记住这件事
that E.H.I. wants everyone to forget.
有线索了
I got something.
我在查看长岛最佳伴旅酒店的
All right, so I was going through surveillance footage
监控录像
of the Best Traveler inn in Long Island city.
我想看看那三个自首的人
I wanted to see if any of our three confessors
是否参加过永恒视野的活动
did attend that E.H.I. Event.
有吗
And...?
没看到他们几个  但是我发现了这个
No sign of them, but I did see this.
那是被害人  看看他和谁在一起
That's our victim. And look who he's with.
鲍尔博士没有说真话
Dr. Bauer lied to us.
他认识贾斯汀
He did know Justin.
我们现在有足够证据拿到搜查令了吗
We got enough for a warrant now?
拜托  你们不能拿走这些文件
Please, you can't take those files!
是吗  搜查令上可不是这么写着的
Really? That's not what my warrant says.
说吧  鲍尔博士在哪
Now, where's Dr. Bauer?
我跟你说过  他在斯德哥尔摩
I told you, he's in Stockholm!
斯德哥尔摩的哪儿  住什么酒店
Where in Stockholm? What hotel?
我不知道
I don't know!
他没把联系电话留给我
He didn't leave a contact number!
探长  我追踪到
Detective, I traced the signal
上次贝克特探长和鲍尔视频通话的信号
from Bauer's video conference with detective Beckett.
他在斯德哥尔摩的什么位置
So where in Stockholm is he?
是这样的
That's the thing.
信号经由斯德哥尔摩
The signal was routed through Stockholm,
但好像是由本地的互联网地址发出的
but it looks like it originated from a local I.P. Address.
本地的  在曼哈顿吗
Local, as in Manhattan?
就在这栋楼里
As in inside this building.
什么位置
Where?
你们不能去那  这是不对外开放的区域
You can't go back there! This -- this area's restricted!
那个房间
That one.
不准动
Don't move!
这就是所谓的斯德哥尔摩
So this is Stockholm.
好吧  是的  我认识他
All right. Yes. I knew him.
可对于他的死我一无所知
But I know nothing about his death.
那你还在销毁文件
And yet you were shredding files,
那些关于安妮塔  萨姆  德怀特  马德森
files on Anita, Sam, Dwight, Madsen --
所有涉案人员的文件
all people connected with this case.
那天发生了什么事  为什么你和贾斯汀会在那
What happened that day? Why were you there with Justin?
我们只是要拍一部电影
All we did was make a film.
电影
A film?
我没有杀他
I didn't kill Justin.
我请他来当演员
I hired him as an actor.
这是我们图像疗法的试点项目
It was part of our image therapy pilot program.
恭候你多时了  进来吧
Been waiting for you. Come on in.
给你拿点水喝
Let me get you a water.
电影是为了让观众
The viewer was supposed to
能将他们的问题发泄到一个人身上
project their problems on a person --
这个案例中  贾斯汀扮演的就是那个人
In this case, Justin.
这就是安妮塔把酗酒的问题怪到他头上的原因
That's why Anita blamed him for her drinking,
也是他成了萨姆易怒情绪聚焦点的原因
and -- and why he was the focus of Sam's anger issues.
我就知道  你在给他们灌输记忆
I knew it. You were implanting memories.
不是的
No!
不是的  这是为了帮助他们学会控制
No, it was supposed to help them take control
通过假想把这些问题击毙
of their problems by literally shooting them dead.
我们拍了两个版本
We -- we made two versions,
一个适用于女士  一个适用于男士
one for women and another for men.
为了激发疗效  我们必须使患者
For the therapy to work, we had to put subjects
处于药物诱导的催眠暗示状态
in a chemically induced suggestive state
然后向他们展示这段录像  但是这太真实了
while showing them this footage, uh, but it was just too real.
这段经历深深地印在他们脑海里
They began to internalize the experience.
他们就真的开始相信
And then they -- they started to believe
是自己杀死了贾斯汀
they'd actually killed Justin.
我们立刻叫停了这个项目
We -- we halted the program immediately.
但却已经造成了伤害
But the damage was already done.
他们扬言要告我们
They threatened to sue.
说我们把他们当成了实验的小白鼠
They said we were using them as guinea pigs.
你就是这么做的
Which you were.
我们只是想帮他们
We tried to help them.
我们召回了这些成员做最后的疗程
We brought them back for one final session
用来  改正错误
to...correct the problem.
你说的改正
And by correcting,
就是对他们使用药物吗
you mean dosing them with propranolol
这样就能让他们忘掉自己来过你这里
so that they would forget they ever visited E.H.I.?
我们只是想帮助人而已
We were just trying to help people.
所以你就派马德森杀贾斯汀吗  来帮他
Is that why you sent Madsen after Justin -- to "Help" Him?
马德森只是提醒贾斯汀
Madsen only talked with Justin
要记得保密协议上的规定
to remind him of the confidentiality agreement
防止他跟别人说起这个项目
that prohibited him from talking about the program.
对他被谋杀这件事  我们确实不知情
We knew nothing about his murder.
可死亡现场被布置得和播放的视频一模一样
And yet his death was staged to mirror that video exactly.
我们想要让这一切
Why would we do that
不被人发现  为什么要杀人呢
when we were just trying to make this go away?
不对
No, no, no, no, no.
是有人针对我们  某个知道这段录像的人
Someone's targeting us, someone who knew about that tape
想利用这视频诋毁我们
and knew they could use it against us.
可能是某个患者
Uh, uh, one of the other test subjects,
某个员工
someone on the crew.
我需要
I'm gonna need a list
所有知道这视频的人员名单
of all of the people that knew about that video.
确定不要再向舞台前走了
Be sure not to step any further downstage,
不然幕布放下来的时候会打到你的脑袋
or the backdrop will smack you in the head when it flies in.
懂了
Roger that.
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett.
贾斯汀的案子有新进展了吗
Do you have news about Justin's case?
有
We do.
我们认为贾斯汀是由于
We now believe that Justin was killed
他出演的一个视频而被害
because of a video that he acted in.
视频
A video?
那视频是为一个叫永恒视野的组织拍摄的
It was made for an organization called E.H.I.,
恰巧那视频的后期制作是由可汗后期制作的
and it just so happens it was edited by Kahn Post Production.
可汗后期
Kahn Post?
帕姆  那不是你上班的地方吗
Pam, isn't that where your day job is?
是  但我不知道视频的事
Yeah, but I don't know about any video.
我们认为你知道
We think you do.
当你看到那视频的时候
And when you saw the video,
你看到了机会
you saw an opportunity.
帕姆  我们查过你的信用卡
Pam, we checked your credit card.
我们知道你刚买了一个翻盖手机
We know that you just bought a flip phone.
所以呢
So?
在贾斯汀被害前
So just before Justin died,
他用翻盖手机给某人发信息
he was texting someone on a flip phone,
据我们推测正是杀害他的凶手
presumably his killer.
当我们查看电话记录时
When we looked into the phone records,
我们查到了宣称是从永恒视野发给贾斯汀的信息
there were texts supposedly from E.H.I. to Justin,
说要付他五千美金再次出演视频中的角色
offering him $5,000 to reprise his role in that video.
我打赌那个电话是你给贾斯汀的
I'm betting that you gave Justin that phone,
或许你跟他说这是永恒视野的人
probably told him someone from E.H.I.
送过来给他的
dropped by, wanted him to have it.
但发信息的并不是永恒视野的人  而是你
But it wasn't E.H.I. that sent those texts. It was you.
你把他骗去了那个酒店  然后杀了他
You lured him to that hotel, and then you killed him.
等一下  这太疯狂了
Wait. This is crazy.
贾斯汀是我的朋友
Justin was my friend.
我为什么要这么做
Why would I do that?
我们查过你的背景  帕姆
We checked your background, Pam.
在永恒视野蒸汗屋入会仪式中
One of the men that was killed
被害的其中一人是阿兰·克拉克
in that E.H.I. sweat-lodge initiation was Alan Clark...
也就是你弟弟
your brother.
永恒视野本该对此负全责
E.H.I. was to blame,
但却没人为此付出代价
but no one was held accountable.
他的死亡被认定是意外
His death was ruled accidental.
当你看到那视频
And when you watched that video,
你意识到这是你干掉他们的最好机会
you realized you had the perfect chance to take them down.
但你知道你需要贾斯汀
But you knew that you needed Justin
来实施这一计划
in order to pull it off,
于是你就找到了一个接近他的机会
so you found a way to get close to him.
天啊  这才是你加入我们戏剧公司的原因
Oh, my God. That's why you joined our theater company.
帕姆  你干了什么
Pam, what did you do?
你不明白
You don't understand.
我必须这么做  为了阿兰  为了其他人
I had to do it -- for Alan, for the others.
必须有人阻止那些恶魔
Those monsters had to be stopped.
通过谋杀一个无辜的人吗
By killing an innocent man?
贾斯汀才不无辜呢  他是跟他们一伙的
Justin was not innocent. He was one of them.
他只是个演员  临时出演一天而已
He was just an actor, hired for the day.
那当我试图跟他谈那件事的时候
Then why did he stonewall me
他为什么闭口不谈
when I tried to talk to him about it?!
他们都要为此负责
They are all accountable!
必须有人阻止他们
Somebody had to stop them!
必须有人把他们的真面目昭告世人
Somebody had to show the world what they really are!
帕姆  转过身去  你被捕了
Pam, turn around. You're under arrest.
所以这一切都是出于报复吗
So all of this was about revenge?
是的  不幸的是
Yeah, and, unfortunately,
你们恰巧被卷入其中
you just got caught in the middle.
那鲍尔博士呢
What about Dr. Bauer?
永恒视野已被取缔
E.H.I. has been shut down, effective immediately,
而联邦调查局也对他们展开了全面调查
and the FBI is launching a full-scale investigation.
那个开红色货车  给我们下药的人呢
And the guy in the red van, the one who drugged us?
边境巡警在他试图跨境去加拿大的时候把他逮住了
Border patrol caught him trying to cross into Canada.
他正被遣返回来
He's being extradited back here now.
我不明白的是
What I don't understand
我们怎么会都来自首呢
is what made us come in when we did,
而且还都在同一天
all on the same day.
霍洛维医生猜测这可能是某种心理暗示
Dr. Holloway figures it was some kind of trigger.
也许你们在报纸上看到对此案的某个报道
Maybe you read an article on the murder
或是在电视上看到了新闻
or you saw something on TV.
不管是什么  现在都结束了
Yeah, but whatever it was, it's over now.
你们都自由了
You're all free to go.
德怀特  你没事吧
Dwight, are you okay?
没  没事
Uh, it's -- it's nothing.
别这样  说说嘛
No, what?
只是我一直都没机会自首
I just never got to confess.
如果你说出来会开心点的话  我愿意当听众
Well, if it makes you feel better, I'll hear it.
我也愿意  走吧  我请客吃披萨
Yeah. Me, too. Come on. I'll buy us all a slice.
好吧
Okay, uh...
我走到147房间  敲了敲门
So, I-I walk up to room 147, knock on the door...
要是再让我听一遍那个自首的话
If I have to hear that confession one more time,
我非杀人不可
I'm gonna shoot somebody.
来  这个东西可以帮你遗忘
Here's a little something to help you forget.
没事的  卡塞尔
It's okay, Castle.
你也知道  我就喜欢怪案
You know I like the weird ones.
有意思的是  人的思想居然可以如此受人控制
It's interesting how malleable the human mind is.
那些人只不过是想寻求一点帮助而已
I mean, all those people wanted was a little help.
结果他们却变成了小白鼠
But instead, they became guinea pigs,
就因为他们求助时找错了人
all because they turned to the wrong person for answers.
是啊  有时候很难分辨
Yeah, well, sometimes it's hard to know
谁才是对的人
who the right person is.
毕竟你也找了三次才找对人
After all, it took you three tries.
的确  但我最终还是找到了呀
True, but I figured it out,
而且还不需要你给我下药
and you didn't even have to drug me.
你怎么知道你睡着了以后我对你做了什么
How do you know what I do to you when you're sleeping?
不管你对我做了些什么  下次叫醒我就是了
Well, whatever it is, wake me up for it next time.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
阿丽克西斯
Alexis.
怎么了
What's going on?
爸
Dad
我能回家吗
can I come home?
过来
Come here.